# CALEB BONFIELD

Narangba, QLD

M: 0451 152 135 | See caleb.bonfield@gmail.com

Github: @Antifact

### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Personable, results-driven Software Engineer with experience in multiple industry-relevant software. Possesses a solid foundation in a variety of programming languages. Outstanding communicator able to work efficiently with diverse colleagues to produce results with precision and punctuality.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

•	HTM	1L5
---	-----	-----

- ReactJS
- APIs
- VMware Workstation 2012-2014
- CSS3
- NodeJS
- Pvthon3
- Deployment Microsoft Server 2012
- Ruby on Rails
- MERN Stack
- Microsoft Server 2012 AD
- Cisco CCNA R&S

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# GPC ASIA PACIFIC | BRISBANE | 2021 - PRESENT

### **Team Leader / Warehouse Assistant (2021-Present)**

- Proactively ensured high standards were maintained and was responsible for product quality control of over 100,000 products.
- Oversaw the evaluation and development of over staff, contributing to overall improvement in operation efficiency and equipping staff members with the skills to be able to apply their knowledge.
- Liaised frequently with upper management to prevent errors, maintain high levels of efficiency, and optimize performance
  of staff.
- Accurately recorded shortages and discrepancies to ensure stock take was conducted precisely. Additionally, responsible for
  the restocking of inventory and receiving stock through the unloading of shipping containers, preventing issues surrounding
  clients waiting for products.

### DOMINO'S PIZZA | CHERMSIDE | 2018 - 2022

### **Assistant Store Manager**

- Managed a team of over 20 staff and was responsible for the recruitment and training of employees, ensuring they were equipped with the knowledge and skills to work as effectively and efficiently as possible.
- Excelled at customer service and conflict resolution within the staff team, as well as with customers. Maintaining high reviews from customers and providing excellent service through exceptional communication skills.
- Responsible for rostering and store preparations prior to operation to maximise efficiency and result to minimal environmental issues and allowing operations to run smoothly.
- Maintained stock through ordering stock, accurate stock take, and preventing outages of products to prevent any hiccups throughout store hours.

### **SOL FLOOR SANDING & POLISHING | BRISBANE | 2016-2018**

#### Floor Sander (2016-2018)

- Accurately surveying and inspecting existing timber floor to decide the most appropriate method of work to produce the best results and to maximise efficiency.
- Building and maintaining positive customer relationships and rapport, leading to 100% customer satisfaction, and thus, improving repeat customer/business percentages.
- Provided accurate quotes and estimation of project finish times through the utilisation of extensive knowledge and clear communication with customers.
- Managed any customer complaints and arising problems, proactively aiming to maintain a high standard of work to reduce customer issues and deal with any complication as soon as possible.

• Effectively communicating with multiple other tradesmen for any one job, leading to a safer work environment and heightened efficiency.

### **EDUCATION**

### **Coder Academy (2021-2022)**

Diploma of IT

# TAFE Queensland (2017-2018)

Diploma of IT Networking

### St. Eugene College

Queensland School Certificate

### ADDITIONAL CREDENTIALS

### AWARDS AND CERTIFICATES

- Employee of the Quarter (2022) GPC Asia Pacific
- Fastest Store in the World (2022) Domino's Pizza